[UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF GIANTS'
"MEANINGLESS LOVE" PLAYS ON STEREO]
(Kurt:)Okay, now you're starting
to make me mad.
A Homo habilis discovering
his opposable thumbs says, "What?"
(Leonard:)- What?
- Ha-ha.
(Leonard:)I think I've made my point.
Yeah? How about I make a point
out of your pointy little head?
(Sheldon:)Let me remind you, while my moral support
is absolute, in a physical confrontation...
(Sheldon:)...I will be less than useless.
(Leonard:)There's not going to be a confrontation.
(Leonard:)In fact, I doubt
if he can even spell confrontation.
(Sheldon:)C-O-N...
(Sheldon:)Frontation.
- Kurt, put him down this instant.
- He started it.
(Penny:)I don't care, I'm finishing it.
Put him down.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Kurt:)You're one lucky little leprechaun.
(Sheldon:)He's a hobbit.
I got your back.
Leonard, are you okay?